ABDULLAHI SHEHU USMAN

Dodballapura, Karnataka, India



shehuusman139@gmail.com



+91 9686059822



linkedin.com/in/abdullahi-shehu-usman-00959622b

Summary

My name is Abdullahi Shehu Usman, a citizen of Nigeria and I am currently studying Bachelor of Computer Applications in India. I am a teenager, who is willing to learn new things around the world in terms of research, computing, and understanding how leaders contribute on a daily basis so that I will bridge the gaps in literacy and share knowledge and experience with the younger generation.

A life of mine full of wishes and want to be a good and fantastic programmer will lead me to bridge the gaps of literacy and share knowledge and experience with younger ones.

I have 4 months of experience in the IT department as a Data entry with HTML, CSS, and programming skills at Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation.

Experience



IT Support Specialist

NNPC Limited Nov 2019 - Feb 2020 (4 months)

IT Support Specialist

NNPC Limited Nov 2019 - Feb 2020 (4 months)

Education



🤊 Iqrah Accademy Rigasa,Kaduna Nigeria.

secondary school certificate, science 2015 - 2016 Attended Senior Secondary school, with certified SSCE result.



🔘 Nuhu Bamalli Polytechnic, Zaria

Diploma of Education, Computer Science 2018 - 2020 Nuhu Bammali polytechnic Zaria kaduna Nigeria.



GITAM Deemed University

Bachelor's degree, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services 2021 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications

Social Worker, Training Certificate - NNPC Limited

IT-235645

Skills

Computer Science • C++ • Java • HTML • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Programming • Problem Solving • Typing • Microsoft Excel

Honors & Awards



Mr.Africa - GITAM Deemed University

May 2022

I am crowned Mr.Africa at GITAM UNIVERSITY Bengaluru.